{
    "subject": "resource/Albert_King",
    "predicate": "ontology/instrument",
    "object": "resource/Gibson_Flying_V",
    "human_readable": "Albert King plays a Gibson Flying V.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6927450299263,
            "question": "Can you name a famous musician who plays a Gibson Flying V?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4298648536205292,
            "question": "What instrument is associated with Albert King?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37008193135261536,
            "question": "What is the distinctive shape of the Gibson Flying V?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2903090715408325,
            "question": "Is the Gibson Flying V a common guitar model?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2704435884952545,
            "question": "What type of guitar does Albert King play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2489013820886612,
            "question": "Is Albert King known for playing a specific guitar brand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2396448850631714,
            "question": "What type of music genre is often associated with the Gibson Flying V?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15173253417015076,
            "question": "Does Albert King use a unique guitar for his performances?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10384049266576767,
            "question": "What is the name of the guitar model Albert King uses?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04973221942782402,
            "question": "Which Gibson model is popular among blues musicians?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Albert King plays a Gibson Flying V.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7717_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the guitar model Albert King uses?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7717_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Albert King use a unique guitar for his performances?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7717_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of music genre is often associated with the Gibson Flying V?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7717_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7717_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7717_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7717_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7717_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7717_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7717_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7717_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7717_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7717_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7717_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide clear evidence that supports the statement \"Albert King plays a Gibson Flying V.\" Specifically, multiple sources indicate Albert King\u2019s use of this guitar, including his mastery and signature style with it."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}